{
	"data": [
    {
      "question": "Mary went out without ___ saying good-bye.",
      "a": "much as",
      "b": "so much as",
      "c": "as much as",
      "d": "as many as",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "-So....as is used in negative sentences, while as.... as.... is used in affirmative ones",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "39",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "To _________ of my knowledge, there are no adequate books on the subject.",
      "a": "the best",
      "b": "the good",
      "c": "the better",
      "d": "the most",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "- Superlative form: Used when three or more things are being compared \n+ Structure: The +adj +est (One syllable word) ; most+ adj (Two-syllable words) \n+ Good-&gt;best ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "39",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "If he continues drinking, ___ he will lose his job.",
      "a": "less or more",
      "b": "less and less",
      "c": "more and more",
      "d": "sooner or later",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "- Sooner or later: used to say that something is certain to happen at some time in the future, though you cannot be sure exactly when",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "39",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "The New York Philharmonic is the second ___ symphony orchestra in America.",
      "a": "good",
      "b": "better",
      "c": "best",
      "d": "well",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "- The second best: ranks second",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "39",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "American collectors have worked feverishly to uncover and preserve as much of the national folklore ___ before it is all forgotten.",
      "a": "as possible",
      "b": "so possible",
      "c": "as possible can",
      "d": "as possible as can",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "- As soon/quickly/much etc as possible: as soon, quickly etc as you can",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "39",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Houses should be built so as to admit plenty of light as well as of fresh air. The former is ___ necessary ___ the latter to a healthy condition of body.",
      "a": "no more, than",
      "b": "not less, than",
      "c": "not more, than",
      "d": "less, than",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "- Not less.... than: equal or more",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "39",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Forty-two years ___, on a soft spring night when the tulips were blooming on the campus, this man, Sir William Osier, addressed the students of Yale University.",
      "a": "after",
      "b": "latter",
      "c": "later",
      "d": "last",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "- Forty - two years later= forty-two years from now",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "39",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Effort is painful, it may be very painful: and yet, while making it, we feel that it is ___ the work it results in, because, thanks to it, we have drawn from ourselves not only all that was there, but more than was there: we have raised ourselves above ourselves.",
      "a": "so precious, and perhaps precious than",
      "b": "as precious as, and perhaps as more precious than",
      "c": "more precious than, and perhaps as precious as",
      "d": "as precious as, and perhaps more precious than",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "- Positive form of adjective: compare that something is equal to some thing \n- Structure: So....as is used in negative sentences, while as.... as.... is used in affirmative ones \n- The comparative form: Used when two objects or persons are being compared \n- Structure: Adj (One syllable word) + er than; More + adj (Two-syllable words) + than",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "39",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "If the sun were to be extinguished, in a day or two, the whole earth would be fast bound in a frost so terrible, that every animal, every plant would die; we could ___ live in such a frost ___ we could live in boiling water.",
      "a": "no less, than",
      "b": "no more, than",
      "c": "not more, than",
      "d": "less, than",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "- No more ...than: used to emphasize that someone or something does not have a particular quality or would not do something",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "39",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "A child in the first grade tends to be ___ all of the other children in his class.",
      "a": "the same old to",
      "b": "the same age than",
      "c": "as old like",
      "d": "the same age as",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "- The same age as= as young as",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "39",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "1"
    }
  ]
}